[{"answer": " What's the matter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"Caugh", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Alright, my friend, that's enough", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No! I am not going to see a psychiatrist", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want you to go see a psychiatrist", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Why? Why not?! Why won't you go", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Because I don't want to", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, I am not going", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "So, when was the last time you took a class", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Are you psyched", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, my God.  my friend's here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " In my class? my friend's gonna be in my class?", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Sure, Saturday night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Goodnight.  Not just a good night", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Goood Moorrrnninng", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Ha, ha! Nothing like some good solid sack time.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So the nurse was giving her a sponge bath", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, man. Well, I guess you'll be going back to that hospital", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No, you don't understand", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I said,", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, I just, uh, fixed it.. a little bit.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " What? What? Who? M", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No! No! Now! Tell me now! What did he say?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " He asked about me? my friend asked about me?!  What did he say", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "How are these your socks?", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Do you believe this? We're fighting. We're fighting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Me too. I've been yelling at strangers on the street.", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I know how difficult this must have been for you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I thought you were meeting my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, he did", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Contest.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yeah, drove away.. You know, I said 'Hello' to him. You know, he's", "qsentId": 34}]